wetfeet.com 2005-12-14

# WetFeet Inc. Privacy Statement

|   
---  

|    
**WetFeet Inc. Privacy Statement**  
[](http://www.truste.org/ivalidate.php?url=www.wetfeet.com&sealid=101) WetFeet, Inc., is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for [www.wetfeet.com](http://www.wetfeet.com/). It was last updated on 5/5/04.

TRUSTe is an independent, nonprofit organization whose mission is to build users’ trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. Because this website wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, this website has agreed to notify you of: 

  1. What personally identifiable information of yours or third-party personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website 
  2. The organization collecting the information 
  3. How the information is used 
  4. With whom the information may be shared 
  5. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of the information 
  6. The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information under WetFeet control 
  7. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact our webmaster by [e-mail](mailto:webmaster@wetfeet.com). If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or if your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then [contact TRUSTe](http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php). TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the website to resolve your concerns.

The TRUSTe program covers only information that is collected through this website, and does not cover information that may be collected through software downloaded from the site.

**WetFeet's Privacy Policy**  
WetFeet, Inc., has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our strong commitment to privacy. The following statement explains our information-gathering and - dissemination practices for our site on the World Wide Web at [www.wetfeet.com](http://www.wetfeet.com/) (the "Site"). This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically. 

**Your Privacy**  
When we gather information from insiders for Insider Guides and other career research products, we work hard to provide them anonymity. They are understandably concerned about their privacy, and we go to great lengths to ensure that their identity is never released by WetFeet, Inc., to anyone outside of WetFeet. 

WetFeet, Inc., values your privacy too. We only request information absolutely essential to the filling of your order or to understand you better so that we can improve our products and services. We will not release name or contact information to third parties without your consent, unless, of course, you're submitting your identity for a purchase from our Site with a credit card. In that case, we will share necessary billing information information with our credit car processor and shipping information with the shipper you designate. Billing information is sent from WetFeet to our credit card processor, CyberCash. We do not store your payment information on our site; it resides on the secure servers of CyberCash indefinitely.

However, we may comply with any subpoena, order of court, or request by a regulatory or law enforcement agency to gain access to any of the information that we collect.

**Online Forums**  
WetFeet, Inc., offers Online Forums to its members. While WetFeet strives to protect your personal information, we cannot provide security for any of the information that you choose to submit to the Forums, as they are essentially open to the public. Please exercise good judgment and protect your passwords and other account information.

**Cookies**  
At times, we use a feature of your Web browser to send your computer a "cookie," a small data file that's stored on your hard drive. We do not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information from your computer. We use cookies to enhance your experience on our Site and to give you better, more personalized service once you've purchased or registered. Cookies allow us to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our Site. Cookies also help to optimize the user experience in our Online Forums by recognizing your username and flagging new forum activity since your last visit. We use this information for internal use only; we don't share it with others. If you chose to refuse to accept cookies, you will be unable to purchase Insider Guides or access member-only areas, and you may experience other loss in site functionality.

**CareerWatch and RecruitWatch Electronic Newsletters**  
We also provide you with the opportunity to receive selected information about career and recruiting topics through our CareerWatch and RecruitWatch electronic newsletters and other free communications. As a registered user, you may opt out of receiving future mailings by changing your subscription preferences on our Site.

**E-mail-A-Friend**  
If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about content from our site, we ask them for the friend's name and e-mail address. WetFeet, Inc., will automatically send the friend a one-time e-mail inviting them to visit the site. WetFeet uses this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time e-mail and does not store the information after the e-mail is sent. 

**Other Information We Collect and How We Use It**  
Our Site uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. 

The Site registration form requires users to give us contact information, including name and e-mail address, in order to allow us to confirm that the registration is for a valid user. We also ask you to provide us with some additional information, such as your educational background, to better match our information, products, and services with your needs. 

When you make a purchase with WetFeet, Inc., we collect your financial information including credit card number on the order form. We also collect your shipping and billing addresses. Contact information from WetFeet's registration forms is used to send orders and may be used to contact you if there is a problem with your order. 

**Privacy Policies of Other Websites**  
Our Site contains links to other sites, including career-related sites. To provide a seamless experience, we may occasionally use framing. Though your browser may indicate that you are at WetFeet.com, you may be on a partner's site. To determine which site you are on, right-click on the site and then select "Properties." Our Site at [http://www.wetfeet.com](http://www.wetfeet.com/) is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. 

**Privacy Policy Covering Ads on the Website**  
WetFeet, Inc., works with a third party that sends banner advertisements to our Site. To find out more about how DoubleClick manages privacy in conjunction with serving advertisements to this Site, please see [its privacy policy](http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy/default.asp).   
Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (e.g., advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising.

**Security**  
The WetFeet Site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. This includes the use of Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), which encrypts information the user inputs into the website. We store your information in a back-end database. Only WetFeet website administrators have access to this information.

**Choice**  
Our Site provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from WetFeet, Inc., and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. 

WetFeet gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service: 

  1. You can change your subscription preferences in your member registration 
  2. You can e-mail your request to [orders@WetFeet.com](mailto:orders@WetFeet.com). 

**Correct/update**  
WetFeet's Site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. 

  1. You can change your information in your member registration 
  2. You can e-mail your request to [orders@WetFeet.com](mailto:orders@WetFeet.com). 

**What constitutes my acceptance of this Privacy Policy?**  
By using the Site or any services provided through the Site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. WetFeet, Inc., reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by electronic notice posted on our Site. Your continued use of our Site thirty (30) days after such notices are posted will be deemed to be your agreement to the changed terms. You may contact WetFeet, Inc., to opt out of any uses of your information that you do not want to participate in.

**Contacting the Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, you can contact us in the following ways: 

**By e-mail:**  

**By snail-mail:**  
WetFeet, Inc.   
The Folger Building   
101 Howard Street, Suite 300   
San Francisco, CA 94105 

**By telephone:**   
415-284-7900   
800-926-4JOB

|
